<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./workflow_writer.png" type="Sink"
	xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v4.1"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v4.1 http://knime.org/node/v4.1.xsd">
	<name>Workflow Writer</name>
	<shortDescription>
		Writes a workflow from a port object into a directory or an exported KNIME workflow (.knwf) archive.
	</shortDescription>
	<fullDescription>
		<intro>
			Writes a workflow from a port object into a directory or an
			exported KNIME workflow (.knwf) archive.
		</intro>
		<tab name="Options">
			<option name="Write to">
				Select a file system to write to.
				There are four default file system
				options to choose from:
				<br />
				<ul>
					<li>Local File System:
						Allows you to select a directory from your
						local system.
					</li>
					<li>Relative to:
						Allows you to choose whether to resolve the path
						relative to the
						workflow, mountpoint or node.
					</li>
					<li>Mountpoint:
						Allows you to choose a mountpoint.
						Whenever this is
						selected, a new drop-down menu appears to choose from
						available
						mountpoints.
					</li>
					<li>Custom URL:
						Uses the standard URL handler providing the ability
						to read a file
						from
						URLs (e.g. file, http or KNIME protocol).
						Browsing and reading folders as well as several of the options
						below are
						disabled when writing to a Custom URL.
					</li>
				</ul>
				It is possible to use other file systems with this node.
				To this end,
				you have to enable the file system connection input port of this
				node
				by clicking the
				<b>...</b>
				in the bottom left corner of the node's icon and choose
				<i>Add File System Connection port</i>
				.
				Afterwards, you can simply connect the desired connector node to
				the
				Workflow Writer node.
				The file system connection will then be
				shown in
				the drop down menu.
			</option>
			<option name="File / URL">
				Enter a valid destination.
				Depending on the selected file system this
				is either a path or a URL pointing to a directory.
				<br />
				You can also choose a previously selected file/folder from the
				drop-down list, or select a destination from the
				&quot;Browse...&quot; dialog.
			</option>
			<option name="Timeout (ms)">
				When writing to a custom URL, this value
				determines the maximum amount of time in milliseconds to establish a
				connection.
			</option>
			<option name="Overwrite folder content if exists">
				This checkbox determines whether to overwrite
				existing files in the selected destination folder.
			</option>
			<option name="Create parent directories if required">
				If checked, any parents of the destination folder
				that do not exist
				yet
				are created.
			</option>
			<option name="Export workflow as knwf archive">
				If the workflow should be written as .knwf
				archive
				instead of a directory.
			</option>
			<option name="Open after write">
				Determines whether the workflow should be opened
				in KNIME Analytics Platform
				after it has been written to a local
				workspace.
			</option>
			<option name="Use custom workflow name">
				If checked, a custom workflow name is used as
				specified below.
				Otherwise the original workflow name, as shown
				above, is used.
			</option>
			<option name="Custom workflow name">
				A customizable name for the to-be-written
				workflow.
			</option>
		</tab>
		<tab name="Inputs &amp; Outputs">
			<option name="Add Input Node">Allows one to add input nodes connected to
				selected inputs prior writing. Depending on the selected node
				here is
				a limited set of options available to pre-configure the node to be
				added. Furthermore, if tabular input data is stored with the input,
				it is used as examples input data for added input nodes.
			</option>
			<option name="Add Output Node">Allows one to add output nodes connected to
				selected inputs prior writing. Depending on the selected node
				there is a limited set of options available to pre-configure the
				node to be added.
			</option>
		</tab>
	</fullDescription>
	<ports>
		<inPort index="0" name="Workflow">
			The workflow to be written.
		</inPort>
		<dynInPort insert-before="0" name="File system connection"
			group-identifier="File System Connection">
			The file system connection.
		</dynInPort>
	</ports>
</knimeNode>